sng.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Swing Left

Effective and Last Updated: 20 December 2016

This website is owned and operated by Swing Left and we have a firm commitment to your privacy and Internet privacy in general. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors and users while they interact with the content and services on this site (www.swingleft.org, the “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site only. It does not apply to other web sites to which we may link. We do gather certain types of information about our users, so we want you to understand what information we collect about you, how we collect it, how that information is used, and how you can control our disclosure of it. You agree that your use of the Site signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site.

1\. Information Collected

We collect two (2) types of information from you: 1) information that you voluntarily supply in form fields on this Site (e.g. through a voluntary registration process, or sign-up for eMail); and 2) information that may be derived through automated tracking mechanisms.

1.1. Voluntary Information for Services and Features

We collect personally identifiable information when you choose to use certain other features of the Site, including: a) consenting to receive eMail or text messages about upcoming events, b) consenting to receive eMail, or c) participating in any interactive or social media as part of the Site. When you choose to use these additional features, we may require you to provide your “Contact Information” in addition to other personal information that may be required to complete a transaction.

1.2. Cookies

Our site uses “cookies” and other web tracking technologies. Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. If a user’s system is idle for a defined time, the cookie may expire, and if so, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized access to the user’s information while they are away from their computer.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you may need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Site.

2\. How We Use Your Information

swingleft.org only uses your personal information for the original purposes it was given. Your personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your approval at the time of collection. In fact, unless otherwise announced, Swing Left has no intention of sharing your personal information for free or sold to any unaffiliated third party.

Swing Left will not disclose, use, give or sell any personal information to third parties.

Please note that personally identifiable information is used only to provide you with a more enjoyable, convenient online experience and to help us identify and/or provide information that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including without limitation: tracking eMail we send to you; and otherwise supporting your use of the Site.

We may permit certain trusted third parties to track usage, analyze data such as the source address that a page request is coming from, your IP address or domain name, the date and time of the page request, the referring Web site (if any) and other parameters in the URL. This is collected in order to better understand our Web site usage, and enhance the performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site. We may use third parties to host the Site; operate various features available on the Site; send you eMail; analyze data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders.

swingleft.org may disclose Contact Information in special cases where we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions of use or may be causing injury or interference with our rights, property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities.

We are not liable or responsible for personally identifiable or other information you choose to submit on any publicly accessible area of the Site.

You will receive notice when your personally identifiable information might be provided to any third party for any reason other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you will have an opportunity to request that we not share such information.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design the Site and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

3\. How We Protect Your Information

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We take appropriate security measures to protect your information against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information and data stored on our system. While no computer system is ever completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

4\. Email Choice/Opt-out

If any user who receives an eMail from the Site and would prefer not to receive such communications in the future, [he or she] can do so by following the instructions in the eMail, where applicable. In addition, you may send an eMail to team@swingleft.org. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to implement your opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive communications from us for up to ten business days as we process your request.

5\. Disclaimer to Security

By consenting to the Privacy Policy, you consent that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk.

6\. Notification of Changes

swingleft.org reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. If at some point in the future, there is a change to our Privacy Policy, unless we obtain your express consent, such change will only apply to information collected after the revised Privacy Policy took effect. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

7\. Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please contact:

team {at} swingleft.org
